
export const quizQuestions_1 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What differentiates a functional component in React from a standard JavaScript function?',
      choices: ['Functional components accept arguments called "props"', 'Functional components can return JSX', 'Functional components are written using ES6 syntax', 'Functional components are executed during the build process'],
      correctAnswer: 'Functional components can return JSX',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in JavaScript?',
      choices: ['var', 'let', 'var and let', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'var and let',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using JavaScript?',
      choices: ['document.write()', 'console.log()', 'window.alert', 'All of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
    },
    {
      question: 'How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?',
      choices: ['const', 'var', 'let', 'constant'],
      correctAnswer: 'const',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in JavaScript?',
      choices: ['stringify()', 'parse()', 'convert()', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'stringify()',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in JavaScript?',
      choices: ['var', 'let', 'var and let', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'var and let',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using JavaScript?',
      choices: ['document.write()', 'console.log()', 'window.alert', 'All of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
    },
    {
      question: 'How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?',
      choices: ['const', 'var', 'let', 'constant'],
      correctAnswer: 'const',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using JavaScript?',
      choices: ['document.write()', 'console.log()', 'window.alert', 'All of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
    },
    {
      question: 'How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?',
      choices: ['const', 'var', 'let', 'constant'],
      correctAnswer: 'const',
    },
  ],
}